onsemi.com 2017-06-02

# Privacy Policy

> ON Semiconductor respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it. This privacy statement explains our policies and practices while you visit our site. Through this disclosure, we intend to provide you a level of comfort and confidence in how we collect, use and safeguard personal and other information that we collect or that you provide through this website. By using the site, you agree to the terms of this privacy statement.
> 
> ## Data Collected
> 
> We collect two types of information: personal and demographic. Personal information is any information that is specific to your identification such as name, address, phone number, email, payment card, resumes, and investor interest. Demographic information is information that cannot be associated with you personally such as, domain information, zip codes and areas of interest. When you provide information for a third party, such as his or her name email and phone number, we assume that the third party has authorized you to do so. 
> 
> ## Use of Data
> 
> When you request a service, place an order, submit feedback, submit a resume, or participate in a seminar or survey, it is necessary for you to offer certain personal information about yourself so that we may serve your needs. We will not send you information unless you specifically request it or we feel that the information would benefit your business needs. If you decide that you do not want to receive further information, simply contact us and request to be removed from the contact list. When you order a sample from us, a customer representative may contact you. The demographic information collected through our site is used to evaluate how our site is used and how it can be improved. It may also be used for marketing, recruiting, and investment analysis. 
> 
> ## Access to your Personal Information
> 
> Our web site allows you to set up a personal account to interact with the company, e.g. to order samples or apply for a job. You may access your personal account to change your personal information.
> 
> ## Cookies
> 
> Some features of this site use cookies or similar technologies such as pixel tags, web beacons, clear GIFs, JavaScript, or local storage. Cookies are small files that the site places on your hard drive for identification purposes. If your browser is set to accept cookies, then your browser adds the text in a small file. Please note that cookies cannot read information on your hard drive. We use cookies to measure our web trafficking processes, so that we may make our site more efficient. We also use cookies to offer you certain services and to customize your visit, and we may use third-party service providers who may use cookies to support our effort to improve our site. You may choose to turn off cookies completely, but you will not be able to use certain site services, such as the shopping cart. 
> 
> If you are a registered user, you can specifically request that our site remembers your login information. By doing so, you are allowing us to place a permanent cookie onto your computer. 
> 
> We use software such as Google Analytics, a first-party cookie that allows us to see information on user website activities including, but not limited to page views, source and time spent on website. The information is depersonalized and is displayed as numbers, meaning it cannot be tracked back to individuals. This will help to protect your privacy. Using software such as Google Analytics, we can see what content is popular on our website, and strive to give you more of the things you enjoy reading and watching. To opt out of Google Analytics analytic cookies across ON Semiconductor websites visit: <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>
> 
> If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies, or to warn you before a cookie is placed. If you choose not to accept cookies, you may have to manually input user IDs and passwords to receive certain data. 
> 
> We also may use cookies for ad serving through software such as Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Hawaii, you may see Hawaii hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). These cookies use “non-personally identifiable information”; they do NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting: [http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/opt-out.html ](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/opt-out.html)
> 
> ## Creating Log-in Credentials
> 
> Certain pages of this website may allow you to create login credentials by creating a user name/ID and password. When you become a registered user you are allowing us to place a permanent cookie onto your computer. 
> 
> You may choose to turn off cookies completely, but you will not be able to use certain site services, such as the shopping cart. 
> 
> ## Disclosure to Third Parties
> 
> In order to offer certain services, ON Semiconductor hires subcontractors to ease business transactions. In the event that we share your personal information with these subcontractors, they will use your personal information for the sole purpose of providing the specific service they are hired for. They will not share your personal information with any third parties. 
> 
> We may also access or disclose your personal information to comply with the law or legal process; to exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; to investigate, prevent, or act against illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to safety, or violations of ON Semiconductor’s terms of use; to protect our operations, assets, and intellectual property; to allow us to pursue appropriate legal remedies or limit damages; to pursue any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer of assets, or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets, or stock; or as otherwise required by law. 
> 
> As a global company, ON Semiconductor may transfer your personal information to any affiliated company or third party for purposes of processing or storage. By providing any personal information to us, you consent to the transfer, processing, and storage of such information including outside of your home country where data protection standards may be different. 
> 
> ## Social Media
> 
> Our site includes areas where you can provide comments about our products and services, and includes links to social media sites that also allow you to post comments about our products and services. Any comments that you post are visible to the public and thus you should have no expectation of privacy with regard to information that you post. We monitor our social media sites and may delete any comments that are offensive, contain links to irrelevant blogs or websites, or are completely unrelated. Also, the third party social media sites that provide platforms for our information have their own privacy policies that govern their sites. 
> 
> ## Children's Privacy
> 
> ON Semiconductor does not collect the personal information of children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have collected children's personal information we will delete the information from our systems unless you provide verifiable parental consent. ON Semiconductor requires that you be 18 years of age to work in any of our facilities. 
> 
> ## Your California Privacy Rights
> 
> ON Semiconductor does not provide personal information to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. Therefore we do not maintain the list of third parties that receive your personal information described in California Civil code Section 1798.83.
> 
> ## Security
> 
> Systems that store your information are firewall protected. Access to sensitive information is restricted to authorized personnel. If we ask for any credit card or financial information, this information is transmitted through Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, which encrypts sensitive information. Information that is transmitted between our site and our registered users is also SSL encrypted. 
> 
> ON Semiconductor is committed to securing the data in which we are entrusted. Unfortunately, no data transmission or storage system is guaranteed to be 100% secure. If you believe that your data is not secure, e.g. if your Log-In Credentials have been compromised, please contact us. 
> 
> ## Related links
> 
> ## Contact Us
> 
> If you have any questions or comments regarding this privacy policy, please contact us and a legal representative will respond to your question/comment. 
> 
> ## Updates
> 
> Occasionally we may update the privacy statement for ON Semiconductor in order to reflect any changes to our website or our privacy practices. If we make any updates to this statement the new statement will be posted to the website ten (10) days prior to the changes taking effect. 
> 
> The effective date of this privacy statement is October 15, 2015.
